<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Marek Slabicki</title>
    <link>https://thaniri.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Marek Slabicki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thaniri.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-09-30-logbook</title>
      <link>https://thaniri.com/blog/2018-09-30-logbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thaniri.com/blog/2018-09-30-logbook/</guid>
      <description>Logbook Structure I&amp;rsquo;m going to start writing a logbook. In it will be a description of what I learned in the course of working on a side project that weekend. The idea comes to me as an easy way to recount what I did, share the lessons learned, and enforce more discipline in consistently working on my side projects.
I imagine it will look something like this:
 Summary  Task Item  Lessons learned  Task Item  Lessons learned    My goal for this blog is not to be useful only to me, but also for my notes to be useful to others who may be trying to learn the same things as myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://thaniri.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thaniri.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Systems Administrator working in a Devops role.
This means that, in addition to traditional sysadmin and networking skills, my skillset checks off some popular buzzwords like:
 Infrastructure as Code Configuration Management Continous Integration Loadbalancing Cloud/On-prem Hybrid Infrastructure  In order to maintain some modicum of programming proficiency, I also work on purely web development focussed side projects.
This website is my place to return some of the knowledge I have gained back to the communities who helped me learn, as well as show off some of the cool things that I have independently done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>